funtvtab.com 2018-08-17

# 

Funtvtab \- Privacy Policy

[Last Modified: March 12, 2018]

Imali Media. (“we”, "us" or the "Company") respects your privacy and is committed to protect the privacy of its users (“user(s)” or “you”).

This Privacy Policy (“Privacy Policy”) sets forth the privacy practices which apply to users that use our new tab extensions or search extensions as detailed in our End User License Agreement (http://funtvtab.com/terms) (“EULA” or “Agreement”) ("Browsing Product" or “Product”).

This Privacy Policy is an integrated part of the Company's EULA (http://funtvtab.com/terms) and is a legally binding agreement between the user and the Company.  The Privacy Policy and EULA shall be binding upon any user using or attempting to use the Browsing Products or any content available therein. 

ACCEPTANCE OF THE TERMS: BY DOWNLOADING OR INSTALLING OR USING THE BROWSING PRODUCT OR OUR SERVICES, AS APPLICABLE, YOU HEREBY AGREE TO THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND THE EULA AND TO THE ACCESS, COLLECTION, USE AND DISCLOSURE OF CERTAIN INFORMATION, AS DESCRIBED IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND IN THE THIRD PARTY’S POLICIES (AS DEFINED BELOW). IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THESE TERMS, PLEASE DO NOT ACCESS, INSTALL, DOWNLOAD OR USE THE BROWSING PRODUCT OR SERVICES.

Further, by downloading or installing or using the Browsing Product or our services, or by accepting this Privacy Policy and the EULA, you also consent to the following privacy policy of Yahoo, whose product might be offered to you as part of our service, available in the following link:  [https://info.yahoo.com/privacy/us/yahoo/search/details.html ](https://www.google.com/url?q=https://info.yahoo.com/privacy/us/yahoo/search/details.html&sa=D&ust=1523346487047000) ("Third Party's Policies"). 

In our Privacy Policy, you will learn about:  
  
---  
  
  * What type of information we collect.

|   
  
  * How we collect your information.

|   
  
  * How we use the information we collect.

|   
  
  * With whom we share the information, and for what purpose.
  * Cookies and other technologies we or third parties may use
  * Links to third party content may presented to you.

|   
  
  * For how long we retain the information we collect.
  * Your choices and control
  * How we safeguard your information.

|   
  
  * Children's information

|   
  
  * Updates or amendments to the Privacy Policy

|   
  
  * How to contact us

|   
  
WHAT TYPE OF INFORMATION WE COLLECT?

The first type of information is non-identifiable information, which may be made available or gathered via the user's use of the Browsing Products or bundle plugins (“Non-Personal Information”). We are not aware of the identity of the user from which the Non-Personal Information was collected.  

The Non-Personal Information which is being collected may include your aggregated usage information and technical information transmitted by your device, including certain software and hardware information as follows:

  * Type of browser, including your default browser;
  * Operating system your device uses;
  * Language preference;
  * The ways in which you use various features of the Browsing Product, your time of access and the domain name of the website from which you linked to the Browsing Products; 
  * We also may periodically collect usage statistics from users that describe the frequency of use of each feature;
  * When you use Browsing Product, the searches you perform using our domains, for example: we may collect information about page views, impressions and clicks, as well as similar web usage information on our domains.

We may disclose or share Non-Personal Information with third parties as specified below and solely if applicable. 

The second type of information is individually identifiable information, namely information that identifies an individual or may with reasonable effort identify an individual (“Personal Information”). The Personal information includes information which was either voluntarily submitted by you when and if you contact us (name, email address, etc.). To clarify, you can use the Product and services without providing us with any contact information. In addition, we collect you IP address through your use of the Product. Note that, while IP address is not considered personally identifiable information in many jurisdictions, there are jurisdictions (such as the EU), in which IP Address may be considered “Personal Information”. Therefore, we treat the user’s IP address as Personal Information, in accordance with applicable laws.

Nonetheless, if we combine Personal Information with Non-Personal Information, the combined information will be treated as Personal Information for as long as it remains combined. 

USE OF INFORMATION WE COLLECT

We use the information collected to: (i) respond to user’s requests, support and, if applicable, investigate any issues a user raises; (ii) send periodic emails or to keep user informed with updates; (iii) enable the Browsing Product to work as is intended, maintain, measure, improve and customize our Browsing Product to your needs and interests and provide you with such content we believe may interest you.

SHARING INFORMATION WITH THIRD PARTIES 

Company will not share any Personal Information collected from you with third parties or any of our partners except in the following events: 

  1. Authorized Disclosures: we may disclose your personal information to third parties when you consent to a particular disclosure of your personal information. Please note that once we share your information with third party, that information becomes subject to the other third party’s privacy practices. 

  2. Compelled Disclosures: we will share your information, solely to the extent needed to comply with any applicable law or permitted by it, regulation, legal process or governmental request (e.g., pursuant to law enforcement inquiries, subpoenas or court orders), or when we believe, in good faith, it is required in order to enforce our policies (including our policies and agreements) including investigations of potential violations thereof or to detect, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities or other wrongdoing, suspected fraud or security issues. In addition, we will share your information, solely to the extent needed to establish or exercise our rights to defend against legal claims or to prevent harm to the rights, property or safety of us, our users, yourself or any third party or for the purpose of collaborating with law enforcement agencies or in case we find it necessary in order to enforce intellectual property or other legal rights. 

  3. Business Transfers. we may share Personal Information, in the event of a corporate transaction (e.g. sale of a substantial part of our business, merger, consolidation or asset sale). In the event of the above, our affiliated companies or acquiring company will assume the rights and obligations as described in this Privacy Policy. 

  4. Corporate Affiliates: We may also disclose your information to our corporate affiliates in order to help provide, understand, and improve the Product and our affiliates' services, this means we may also internally combine information we have on you.

We may share aggregate or anonymous Non-Personal Information with third party service provider partners (i.e., Google Analytics, Amazon, search feed providers, customer service, marketing assistance, ad tracking, service functionality and support, etc.) (“Service Providers”) and other third parties in accordance with the terms of this Policy. We may store Non-Personal and Personal Information on our servers or our cloud servers, use or share Non-Personal Information in any of the above circumstances, as well as for the purpose of providing and improving our Product. We do not share any Personal Information with Service Providers or any third party thereof, unless indicated otherwise in our Privacy Policy. 

COOKIES AND OTHER TECHNOLOGIES

We and our trusted partners use cookies and other technologies (e.g. web beacons, pixels, etc.) in our related Browsing Products, including when you visit our site or access our Browsing Products. Like many other vendors, we gather some information automatically, such as your usage data, by ourselves or by using third party service and store it in log files.  For more information about how to manage or clean your cookies click here

A "cookie" is a small piece of information that a website assigns to your device while you are viewing a website. Cookies are very helpful and can be used for various different purposes. These purposes include improving the Product, allowing you to navigate between pages efficiently, enable automatic activation of certain features, remembering your preferences and other information that is used on the webpages that you visit, making the interaction between you and our Browsing Products quicker and easier and customize and improve the Product. You can find more information about cookies at  [www.allaboutcookies.org](https://www.google.com/url?q=http://www.allaboutcookies.org&sa=D&ust=1523346487061000) . You may disable and remove some cookies through your device or browser settings. However, if you choose to disable cookies, some features of our Browsing Products may not operate properly and your online experience may be limited. You may control how your browser responds to cookies by adjusting the privacy and security settings of your web browser.

Our Service Providers may also use cookies, scripts or web beacons for the purpose of tracking and analyzing your use, this information does not include Personal Information. To learn more how Google uses data from our use of Google Analytics Cookie we recommend you review Google’s policies located at: [ ](https://www.google.com/url?q=http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners&sa=D&ust=1523346487061000) [www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners](https://www.google.com/url?q=http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners&sa=D&ust=1523346487061000) . We also encourage you to review the Google Analytics' currently available opt-outs for the web tool available at:  [ ](https://www.google.com/url?q=https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/&sa=D&ust=1523346487062000) [https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/](https://www.google.com/url?q=https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/&sa=D&ust=1523346487062000) .

LINKS TO THIRD PARTY CONTENT

Our Product may include links to other third party content (e.g., Gmail, Amazon, Facebook, YouTube etc.), including Service Provider’s content whose privacy practices may differ from those of Browsing Product. Our service may also be linked to sites or services operated by our affiliates or third parties, and may carry advertisements or offer content, functionality, games, or applications developed and maintained by third parties including, any online store. Please note that these features are provided by us only as a suggestion. Browsing Product is not responsible for the privacy practices of any such third parties, and once you leave the Product via a link, enable a third-party service, you should check the applicable privacy policy of the third-party site. Your information is governed by their privacy statements. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy statement of any Web site you visit. 

FOR HOW LONG WE RETAIN THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT?

We may rectify, replenish or remove incomplete or inaccurate information, at any time and at our own discretion. Please note that unless you instruct us otherwise (as detailed below) we retain the Non-Personal Information we collected for as long as needed to provide the Browsing Products and to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes and enforce our agreements. Further, we retain the Personal Information, we collected for as long as legally permissible, in accordance with applicable laws.

YOUR CHOICES AND CONTROLS

We provide you with the ability to exercise certain choices and controls in connection with our treatment of your information. Depending on your relationship with us, these choices and controls may include:

  * Requesting access to the Personal Information collected about you that we hold;
  * Correcting, modifying, updating or deleting the information associated with you that we hold;
  * Object to the collection of Personal Information by us;
  * Transfer Personal Information collected by us; and 
  * Opting-out of targeted advertising, if applicable. In addition, even after providing your consent to this Privacy Policy, you are entitled to change your mind. If you do, you may opt out of the data collection, sharing process and targeted advertising services related to our Browsing Product. Note that once you opt out, part of the service provided by us might no longer be available and some features may not work if you revoke the data transfer. You may opt out of certain third parties’ cookies and browser-enabled, interest-based advertising at the Network Advertising Initiative’s (“NAI”) website-  [NAI consumer opt-out](https://www.google.com/url?q=http://optout.networkadvertising.org/%23/&sa=D&ust=1523346487065000)  and the Digital Advertising Alliance’s (“DAA”) website-  [DAA opt-out page](https://www.google.com/url?q=http://www.aboutads.info/&sa=D&ust=1523346487065000) . Our Service Providers may also provide ways for you to opt out from or limit their collection of information from and about you, such as detailed above or as follows:  [https://aim.yahoo.com/aim/us/en/optout/](https://www.google.com/url?q=https://aim.yahoo.com/aim/us/en/optout/&sa=D&ust=1523346487065000)  

We value your privacy and control over your Personal Information, and therefore you may, at any time, make such request (to object, transfer, access, change, delete, modify, update or remove your Personal Information) by contacting us at:  support(at)imali.media.   

In the event you make such request, note that we may require certain information from you in order to verify your identity and locate your data and that the process of locating and deleting the data may take up until one (1) month in accordance with applicable laws. Data privacy and related laws in your jurisdiction may provide you with different or additional rights related to the data we collect from you, which may also apply. 

HOW DO WE SAFEGUARD AND TRANSFER YOUR INFORMATION?

We take great care in implementing and maintaining the security of the Browsing Products and your information. We employ industry standard procedures and policies to ensure the safety of our users’ information, and prevent unauthorized use of any such information. Although we take reasonable steps to safeguard information, we cannot be responsible for the acts of those who gain unauthorized access or abuse our Browsing Products, and we make no warranty, express, implied or otherwise, that we will prevent such access.

We may adopt what we believe is appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access to such data. If you feel that your privacy was treated not in accordance with our policy, or if any person attempted to abuse our Browsing Products or acted in an inappropriate manner, please contact us directly at  support(at)imali.media  Further, in the event of a data breach, in which we discover your Personal Information is at risk, we will notify you through the Product or, if technically possible, by sending you an email.

MINORS

You represent and warrant that you are at least 13 years of age and of legal competence to enter into these Agreement. If you are under 18, please be sure to read the Agreement with your parents or legal guardians. We do not use the Product to knowingly solicit data from or market to children under the age of thirteen (13). We request that such individuals do not provide Personal Information through our services. 

If you become aware or have any reason to believe that a child under the age of 13 has shared any information with us, please contact us at:   support(at)imali.media  and we take reasonable steps to ensure that such information is deleted from our files. 

TRANSFER OF DATA

We may store or process your information in the United States or in other countries. If you are a resident of the European Economic Area ("EEA") we will take appropriate measures to ensure that your information receives an adequate level of data protection upon its transfer outside of the EEA. If you are a resident of a jurisdiction where transfer of your data requires your consent, then your consent to this Privacy Policy includes your express consent for such transfer of your Personal Information. 

DO NOT TRACK DISCLOSURE

The Browsing Product or our services does not respond to Do Not Track signals. For more information about Do Not Track signals, please see:  [http://www.allaboutdnt.com/](https://www.google.com/url?q=http://www.allaboutdnt.com/&sa=D&ust=1523346487068000) .

AMENDMENTS

We reserve the right to periodically amend or revise the Privacy Policy from time to time, at our sole discretion; Any changes to the Privacy Policy will become effective immediately upon the display of the revised Privacy Policy. The most recent version of the Privacy Policy will always be posted. If we do make any changes, the updated date at the top of the Privacy Policy will be reflected in the "Last Modified" heading. Your continued use of the Browsing Product or our services, following the display of such modified Privacy Policy, constitutes your acknowledgement and consent of such amendments to the Privacy Policy and your agreement to be bound by the terms of such amendments. In the event of a material change we will make best efforts to send you a written notification. 

HOW TO CONTACT US

If you have any general questions about the Browsing Products or the information that we collect about you and how we use it, please contact us at:  support(at)imali.media

Data protection officer- CTO

Our data protection officer's contact details are:  support(at)imali.media .
